<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Member Ryan?</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_content">Content</string>
    <string name="homepage">A new memberry will be delivered every Monday by those who love you and
        occasionally despise you. Tap Randy\'s face to view this week\'s memberry!</string>
    <string name="tomone"
        >A horse. With a saddle. Right next to our house. Member Ryan, I am always watching.
    </string>
    <string name="palione"
        >Member the time we spent the rest of our lives together because I killed Jade
        like a pig taken to the slaughter.</string>
    <string name="joeone"
        >Monday mornings in Ryan\'s armpit on the Central line. So many ideas were discussed in
        that same armpit. Even a musical about the tube. Our bodies were transported from
        Leytonstone to work everyday, but never our ideas from script to screen. Sometimes,
        if I listen close enough when I ride between Bank and Stratford, even now, I can still hear
        those ideas lost on the tracks. They\'re screaming for their parents.
        But we\'re long gone. </string>
    <string name="jadeone"
        >Member when you dyed your hair dark because you thought it looked more
        mysterious?</string>
    <string name="amyone"
        >My favourite thing about you is your deadpan delivery of lines like, "You don\'t know the
        true feeling of loneliness till you spend a day alone in this house" - You were so dry when
        I first met you I didn\’t know if you were joking half the time or not. I thought if you 
        are joking then this guy is fucking hilarious, if not he\'s definitely a psychopath. 
        I now know you\'re a combination of both and have just learnt to accept that without
        question. So, my favourite thing about you is that you\'re 50% psychopath.</string>
    <string name="barryone"
        >What was your hairstyling routine during 2010?</string>
    <string name="ianone"
        >There was once a computer genius who was bored as he sat there at his desk watching the 
        trees of Epping. To amuse himself he took a great breath and sang out "I got 62 on the grip 
        test!". The residents of Whipps gathered round to congratulate the boy on his success. The
        boy laughed out loud, "I made it all up!", the residents of Whipps looked on in disgust. 
        Later that night, the boy sat in bed with the grip test, and, to his delight, he hit a new 
        height, "71, oh what a score!" he roared. But no one came to congratulate the boy, as they
        thought it was, yet again, another ploy.</string>
    <string name="palitwo"
        >Member that time I said Liverpool Street was really close</string>
    <string name="jadetwo"
        >Member little pig voice</string>
    <string name="joetwo"
        >One night out. A photo of Jade\'s arse. A romance that never was - even with Ryan\'s
        encouragement. I think he was trying to be friends. Like when one tribe offers the other
        woman or some kind of livestock as part of a truce. I\'m not intentionally comparing Jade
        to livestock. Just kidding. I am.</string>
    <string name="shabs"
        >Member the horrible game at uni where everyone tried to finger each other? It got to the
        point where everyone was super paranoid, to the extent that you wouldn\'t go up the stairs
        if someone was behind you. One day Andy\'s room was shut giving you the false sense of
        safety. But Andy was just listening, waiting for his moment to pounce. As you walked past,
        Andy leapt out and fingered you, missing your arsehole by a few millimetres. (This bit
        gets graphic.) Andy fingered you so hard that you started bleeding. Because of the
        proximity of the wound,  your arsehole would never heal. Basically, every time you went to
        the toilet your wound would open again. And it is for that reason that, still to this day,
        you have to take wet wipes and cream to the toilet.</string>
    <string name="barrytwo"
        >What is Max\'s birthday</string>
    <string name="tomtwo"
        >One day I will have a child. I will feel an unconditional love for this child that 
        will barely be able to understand. My child and I will share a deep bond woven by genetics.
        But that bond is nothing compared the one we shared when I first played Journey with you. 
        See you in the clouds, my friend.</string>
    <string name="jadethree"
        >Member keeping a twenty pence piece in all of your shoes</string>
    <string name="sarahone"
        >Member when I wished your dog was dead</string>
    <string name="james"
        >Member being weak and having terrible form when we first started gym? Don\'t forget
        to breathe.</string>
    <string name="mikeone"
        >Member how you used to arse lick me and The Fandangos a lot at uni? Used to go on about
        how \'Wild Beast\' was like the perfect indie tune. Anyways, since then it\'s been cool
        discovering the inner you, and all your little crooks and treats. You\'re always going
        to be a shitty spurs fan, but you\'re helpful when I\'m in a tight spot.</string>
    <string name="wardakone"
        >Member spending a night on the street because Freddie Mercury kicked down
        my door.</string>
    <string name="jadefour"
        >Member grapple arm?</string>
    <string name="palithree"
        >Member our first male bonding when I wrapped your face in clingfilm at a party?
        That was when I finally stopped judging you on your hair and on what\'s inside.</string>
    <string name="joethree"
        >Ryan. A cardboard box. A very sharp knife. Pali\'s unnecessarily naked and inadequate
        paper dick. Put it all together and what do you get? Robot Wars.</string>
    <string name="mumone"
        >Member I threatened to tie you to a lamp post if you misbehaved?</string>
    <string name="sarahtwo"
        >Member road trips with Jack, Woody, Joe and I? We\'d all get really drunk and roudy,
        but you couldn\'t because you were pretending to be Ryan Gosling driving the car wearing
        your Drive gloves.</string>
    <string name="tomthree"
        >I member what I said to you one of the first times I met you: "I\'ve heard a lot about you.
        I think we\'re going to be good friends." I was right.</string>
    <string name="jadefive"
        >Member wearing Toms without socks during all types of weather (snow included)?</string>
    <string name="wardaktwo"
        >Member Photoshop?</string>
    <string name="miketwo"
        >So I thought you were pretty quiet, bit weird when I first met you. But that soon
        changed once I discovered he was into making music and general beat making.</string>
    <string name="sarahthree"
        >Member that time you pushed me down the stairs and shoved a Digestive biscuit
        in my mouth?</string>
    <string name="joefour"
        >Ryan must have been a chauffeur for a celebrity in a past life. He makes it a priority to
        get his friends to social gatherings in reasonable time. And when he fails he takes it like
        the loss of a close relative. It\'s like a wizarding dark mark on his good name. One time I 
        remember in particular was when his car broke down before we even began our trip to one of 
        Mike\'s shit parties in Bristol.  I don\'t even remember why we were going to Mike\'s. 
        (Probably some promise of poor quality tapas in meagre supply.) It doesn\'t really matter, 
        because what I do remember is this: Ryan picked up the phone knowing full well he didn\'t 
        have Home Breakdown Cover and that he was going to have to fork out a hefty fee, but still,
        he dialled the AA helpline and swallowed the fee whole like a slice of Nana Bateman\'s 
        filthy sweet tiffin mix. Because that\'s the man he is. A doer. A fighter. A driver. He\'s
        an engine that never asks for a fee. But that time I had to force a £10 note on him. 
        Actually, I can\'t remember if I actually did. I think I made a mental note that I would.
        Is it too late to give it now? Be pretty embarrassing to even bring it up. Fuck it.
        Ryan, if you\'re listening, this is my way of saying thank you. Imagine if you put your hand
        to the tapas as well. What a night that could have been.</string>
    <string name="palifour"
        >Member that time you walked in on me and Jade</string>
    <string name="mumtwo"
        >Member eating microwave pizzas?</string>
    <string name="tomfour"
        >Member when you pooed yourself in front of me? Well I felt it was relevant for this app,
        so I told Sarah. She\'ll probably know this for a few months before you get this
        notification. That\'s why she no longer respects you, in case you were wondering.</string>
    <string name="mumthree"
        >Member me cutting squares out of your blankey when you were naughty?</string>
    <string name="wardakthree"
        >Homeless guy turning into chips</string>
    <string name="jackone"
        >Things I like about you: 1. Your fat fucking lips
                                  2. Your hair when it grows out
                                  3. Your one-evening only moustache
                                  4. Your dancing
                                  5. The fact you never leave the house
                                  6. The way to you talk to people\'s parents</string>
    <string name="jacktwo"
        >Member that time you got too excited and snorted hot pepper dust?</string>
    <string name="jackthree"
        >Member that time you spat on Andy?</string>
    <string name="jackfour"
        >Member that time you held Andy and Jack hostage and forced them to fornicate?</string>
    <string name="jackfive"
        >Member that time your dying wish was a Rustlers burger?</string>
    <string name="jacksix"
        >Member that time you made a real human from nothing but a balloon?</string>
    <string name="jackseven"
        >Member that time you launched a full-scale reconnaissance mission and investigation
        on Wiseman?</string>
</resources>

